Welcome back to my series where I
recreate Ben & Jerry's flavors, but
lower in calories and higher in protein.
This is raspberry cheesecake topped. Let
me show you how to make it. It's 10 out
of 10.
>> The base is a cheesecake base, so it's
essentially my vanilla base, but we're
adding some cream cheese in there, which
makes it super rich and thick. One of my
favorite base flavors. The full
ingredients and amounts will be down in
the description below. We're going to
freeze that for 16 hours, take it out,
run it under hot water for about a
minute, and then throw in the creamy on
the ice cream setting. If this is the
first time you've seen me use the ice
cream setting, that's because it is very
rare for me to do so. Usually the bases
I make have such little fat that they
take much longer to spin. But this one,
which has the fat from the cream cheese
takes a little less time to get to that
consistency we want before adding the
mix-ins. Speaking of the mixins, we're
going with some frozen raspberries and
some kind of graham cracker. I used
Teddygrams. Going to run that on the
mix-ins setting. And then we're going to
top all of this with some white
chocolate melted with coconut oil. And
then a little bit more of that graham
cracker.